ILGWU Audio-Visual (AV) 5780 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Public Service Forum, The Role of Unions in Our Society, 1962 (Box 47a, Folder 17)
  Nov. 29; John I. Snyder, President, U.S. Industries, Inc., interviewed by Ralph Reuter
- Public Service Forum, Do Consumer Laws Protect Us Adequately?, 1962 (Box 47a, Folder 18)
  Dec. 20; Daniel B. Asmuda, Senior Attorney, Federal Trade Commission, interviewed by Ralph Reueter
- Public Service Forum, Fraudulent Pricing, 1963 (Box 47a, Folder 19)
  Jan. 3; Karl Peterson, Manager, Certified Stories, interviewed by Ralph Reuter
- Public Service Forum, Group Relations 1963 (Box 47a, Folder 20)
  Jan. 17; Dr. James M. Eagan, National Vice President, National Conference of Christians and Jews, intereviewed by Ralph M. Reuter
- [unlabeled] (Box 47a, Folder 21)
- [unlabeled] (Box 47a, Folder 22)
- [unlabeled] (Box 47a, Folder 23)
- [unlabeled] (Box 47a, Folder 24)
- [unlabeled] (Box 47a, Folder 25)
- [unlabeled] (Box 47a, Folder 26)
- [unlabeled] (Box 47a, Folder 27)
- [unlabeled] (Box 47a, Folder 28)
- Rally [at Madison Square Garden?]. Writing in a banner in the stage states, Condition Enforcement = Contract. On top of that stage, there are several men seated and a man in delivering a speech at a podium. (Box 48, Folder 10)
  16mm; 3.3 min.
- Local 22 members traveling to Montral (Box 48, Folder 11)
  faded or overexposed in the beginning
- Unity House (Box 48, Folder 12)
  picnic (tail out) shots of people in casual attire hanging out in a park and a house; slightly faded beginning
- Harriman. Local 22. Part 2, 1950 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  faded image
- Mother is on strike, 1959 (Box 48, Folder 137)
  San Antonio, Local 180 struck against Tex-Son; Mothers and children picketing for pay and benefits suffer police brutality
- President Louis Stulberg on television (Box 48, Folder 138)
  June; speech on current labor conditions, then Q and A
- GEB at Work and Play, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 139)
  GEB and membership in activities; labor stage; get together luncheon; Locals 89 and 117
- Unity House, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 139.1)
  betacam and VHS preservation copies
- Funeral of Morris A. Goldstein (Late Secretary-Treasurer). Chicago Joint Board. Amateur movie., 1947 (Box 48, Folder 140)
  16mm; 2 min.; September 1947
- Commencement at Bard College - David Dubinsky receives Honorary Ph. D. Law and Eleanor Roosevelt: Honorary Degree, in same ceremony., 1951 (Box 48, Folder 141)
  16mm; 2.3 min.; June 1951
- Miscellaneous Rallies. Chorus and marching orchestra, as well as Local members, parades, stadium, banners and placards. Anti-Hitler, anti-fascism. (Box 48, Folder 142)
  16mm, 1930s; copy on VHS, V142
- Miscellaneous Rallies. Chorus and marching orchestra, as well as Local members, parades, stadium, banners and placards. Anti-Hitler, anti-fascism. (Box 48, Folder 143)
  16mm; 1930s
- Mark Starr on Labor Education., 1975 (Box 48, Folder 144)
  1 " Audio Tape, 1 3/4" U-Matic; 60 min.; January 22, 1975; 2 parts
- Garment Workers (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Humphrey/Jackson ILGWU in Rhode Island (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Shop time and motion study (Box 49, Folder 11)
- Lurye Memorial Meeting. Rally includes a Dressmakers banner., 1952 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  May 9
- Women sewing by hand (Box 49, Folder 12)
  Shop time and motion study; poorly aligned
- Henry Gans Shop. Women sewing by hand., 1940-1949 (Box 49, Folder 12)
- Elderly man sewing, followed by several other men and women of different ages sewing (Box 49, Folder 14)
  Shop time and motion study
- Shop scenes. Old man, and several other men and women of different ages, sewing, 1960-1969 (Box 49, Folder 14)
- No title (Box 49, Folder 15)
- Workers in a garment shop, 1950-1969 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  out of focus
- Labor-Liberal Rally, 1940-1999 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  Out of focus; did not see in box?
- Bus trip, 1960-1969 (Box 49, Folder 18)
- ILGWU Fellowship in Action (Box 49, Folder 58)
- President Louis Stulberg on TV in Wyoming Valley, PA, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 138)
  June; Missing
- The Fellowship in Action, 1930-1939 (Box 49, Folder 144)
  ILGWU student fellowship plans activities to culturally enrich ILGWU members' lives.
- Always In Fashion, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 145)
- Adlai Stevenson rally at Manhattan Center (Box 49, Folder 146)
  October; Introduction by David Dubinsky, ILGWU, also Robert F. Wagner for Mayor and Estes Kefauver. Discusses crisis with Israel.
- Cloakmakers Joint Board 35th Anniversary Celebration David Dubinsky (Box 49, Folder 147)
- 35th Anniversary Celebration off Cloakmakers ILGWU NY David Dubinsky, 1945 (Box 49, Folder 147)
  December
- No title [Assume Convention, 1980] (Box 50, Folder 242)
  September 28; Would not play
- introduction of General Executive Board of ILG, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 243)
  September 28; ILGWU Chorus, Raymond R. Corbut (President - NYS AFL-CIO), Harry Van Arsdale; audio works; picture disappears and returns, progressively -worse tracking
- End of introductions, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 244)
  September 28; Sandy Meiser(?) introduces Sol Chaikin. Chaikin talks about height of ILGWU membership in 1969, when it had 460,000 members; talks about growing disparity between the "haves" and "have-nots"; calls Jimmy Carter most helpful president to the ILGWU since John F. Kennedy.
- Continuation of Sol Chaikins speech, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 245)
  September 28; Attacks Senator Heinz (PA); supports Carter in 1980, saying he is not perfect but is the best option; compares Reagan to Jesse Helms, Orrin Hatch; talks about continuing education opportunities for ILGWU members, including scholarships for members' children
- End of remarks by Chaikin. Announcements by General-Secretary of the Convention, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 246)
  September 28; shots of slogan banners (ex. "Look for the Union Label" and delegates; no sound at the end, but doesn't miss any speeches
- Resolutions of the Convention (Box 50, Folder 247)
  September 28; Support for ERA and Carter/Mondale 1980. Chaikin introduces Carter. Carter declares US support for Israel at the UN; differentiates between Democratic and Republican political philosophies, gives his support to ERA.
- Continuation of Carters speech, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 248)
  September 28; He defends legal right to organize, collective bargaining. Sol Chaikin speaks again.
- Footage of Carters limo arrival, waving to crowd; cuts to inside convention hall, but no sound; then cuts to convention resolutions (again); returns to Chaikin introducing Carter, and the beginning of Carters speech., 1980 (Box 50, Folder 249)
  September 28; first 2 minutes has sound but no picture
- Resolutions of the Convention, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 250)
- Convention, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 251)
  September 28; Starts the same as v 248, but after Carter's speech it cuts to a "Re-Elect President Carter" dinner; speech by Mario Cuomo introduces Felix [?]. Felix distinguishes Carter from Reagan, advocates for Carter even though he says they do not always see eye-to-eye on economic issues.
- Convention, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 252)
  September 28; NYS Lieutenant Governor Mario Cuomo introduces Ed Koch. Koch talks about NYC as a microcosm of America, and thanks Carter for helping New York get out of debt in 1978. After Koch, Cuomo introduces Governor Hugh Carey; Carey says "How to win New York" starts with "thinking ethnic." Carey's speech gets cut in the middle, and the video picks up immediately with the Governor introducing the President, who begins speaking; first minute has sound but no picture
- Convention, 1980. Continuation of 252 (Box 50, Folder 253)
  September 28; Carter talks about reducing dependency on OPEC; Sound quits as Carter leaves.
- Convention, 1980. (Box 50, Folder 254)
  22 Audio Tapes
- Sunday night Party (Box 50, Folder 255)
- ILGWU Chorus, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  " x 7"; May 27, 1983
- Untitled. Side 1, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 2)
- Untitled. Side 2, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 3)
- Untitled. Side 5, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 4)
- Untitled. Side 6, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 5)
- Untitled. Side 1, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  " x 7"; May 30, 1983
- Untitled. Side 2, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 7)
- Untitled. Side 5, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 8)
- Untitled. Side 6, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 9)
- Untitled. Side 9, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 10)
- Untitled. Side 1, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  " x 7"; May 31, 1983
- Untitled. Side 2, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 12)
- Untitled. Side 3, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 13)
- Untitled. Side 6, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 14)
- Untitled. Side 7, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 15)
- Untitled. Side 1, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  " x 7"; June 1, 1983
- Untitled. Side 2, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 17)
- Untitled. Side 3, 1983 (Box 51a, Folder 1)
- Untitled. Side 6, 1983 (Box 51a, Folder 2)
- Untitled. Side 7, 1983 (Box 51a, Folder 3)
- Untitled. Side 10, 1983 (Box 51a, Folder 4)
- Untitled. Side 11, 1983 (Box 51a, Folder 5)
- Untitled. Side 1, 1983 (Box 51a, Folder 6)
  " x 7"; June 2, 1983
- Untitled. Side 2, 1983 (Box 51a, Folder 7)
- Untitled. Side 5, 1983 (Box 51a, Folder 8)
- Untitled. Side 6, 1983 (Box 51a, Folder 9)
- Untitled. Side 9, 1983 (Box 51a, Folder 10)
- Untitled. Side 10, 1983 (Box 51a, Folder 11)
- Untitled. Side. 1, 1983 (Box 51a, Folder 12)
  " x 7"; June 3, 1983
- Untitled. Side 2, 1983 (Box 51a, Folder 13)
- Untitled. Side 5, 1983 (Box 51a, Folder 14)
- Untitled. Side 6, 1983 (Box 51a, Folder 15)
- Convention, 1983 - Old Camera. (Box 52, Folder 10)
  VHS; 120 min.; Same time frame as v11, with stationary camera not focused on speaker or action.
- Convention, 1983 -New Camera, Tape #1. (Box 52, Folder 11)
  VHS; 120 min.; Includes Conductor Malcolm Dodd and chorus perform "Roll the Union On," "Look for the Union Label," "We Shall Not Be Moved," "We're Gonna Roll the Imports Back," "Solidarity Forever." Temporary Chairman Nick Benarno Reverend Joseph Howell, Charles "Chick" Perez, President of Browert County AFL-CIO, District President of Florida AFL-CIO, and Director of the Gold Coast Electrical Job Training Committee. ILGWU President Sol Chaikin, Secretary Treasurer Shelley Appleton, Executive Vice President Wilbur Daniels, Executive Vice President Frederick Siems. The General Executive Board Matthew Stonewall, Douglas Levine, Edward Schneider, Cornelius Wall, Sol Hoffman, Mattie Jackson, Clifford Depin, Glenwood Clay, Sol Goldberg, Manuel Gonzalez, Gerald Grossman, Frank Longal, Jay Mazur, Sam Leimeizer, Erwin Solomon, Evy Dubrow, Peter Nadash, Joseph Fisher, Luigi Montenegro, and Ronal Hallman. Chaikin speaks for duration of tape.
- Convention, 1983 -New Camera, Tape #2. (Box 52, Folder 12)
  VHS; 120 min.; Chaikin speaks, some overlap with V11. The profile of the union, Canada, Task Forces, leaders, finances, legislation, international trade unions, the members of the Executive Board and their committees.
- Convention, 1983 - Education Committee, Law Committee, Work Standards, officer reports, organization. (Box 52, Folder 13)
  VHS; 120 min.; Chaikin speaks about retirees and their replacements, and Unity House. Several committee meetings including the Education committee (which discussed Publications of Union Materials in other languages and citizenship education).
- Convention, 1983 - Friday 5/27/83- 5/28/83, committees - resolutions, social and labor, ILGWU Institution and Welfare, and International Affairs committees. (Box 52, Folder 14)
  VHS; 120 min.; Resolutions committee discusses abortion and civil rights. Social and Labor Legislation Committee chaired Evy Dubrow discussing Blue-Cross health care, sick benefits, Citizens' Utility Board, and undocumented workers. ILGWU Institution and Welfare committee discuss Health Center and retirement plans. International Affairs discusses solidarity resolutions; May 27, 19/83- May 28, 1983
- Convention, 1983 - New Camera, Monday 5/30/83, Morning Tape #1. (Box 52, Folder 15)
  VHS; 120 min.; Father Lawrence Conway. Reports by Leon Stein (GEB report), Peter Nadash and Gelles Gottier (Credentials), Mattie Jackson and Herbert Dicurtner (Rules), Luigi Montenegro speaks and Shelley Appleton is appointed temporary chair. Volunteer Stipend is discussed at length.
- 1983 Convention-New Camera, Monday 5/30/83, Morning Tape #2, Afternoon Tape #1. (Box 52, Folder 16)
  VHS; 120 min.; Adopting reports. Constitution amendments are passed. Congressmen Claude Pepper speaks on social justice, free trade, American business and social security. Camera does long pans of the banners of the Locals present. Chaikin speaking to Channel 4 News; May 30, 1983
- 1983 Convention-Old Camera, Monday 5/30/83. (Box 52, Folder 17)
  VHS; 120 min.; Resolutions Committee Chair VP Jay Mazur, Manager of Local 23-25 addresses political action, exploitation of undocumented workers, solidarity, employment, putting a ceiling on the Regan tax-break, social services, and lowering interest rates to revive the economy. Erwin Solomon of the Pennsylvania Dress Board and Lillian McKitrick with Resolution Committee's report on civil rights (Dr. King's Birthday as a holiday), amnesty for undocumented workers, energy, public transportation, abortion, solidarity, and changing the name of the ILGWU. Tatanabo Usami of Zensin Dome (Japan's AFL). Usami's speech is delivered by assistant Fukuda on Free-World Trade Union, solidarity, and the promotion of welfare between organizations; May 30, 1983
- 1983 Convention-New Camera, Monday 5/30/83, Afternoon Tape #2. (Box 52, Folder 18)
  VHS; 120 min.; "Look for the Union Label" in multiple languages. Same content as V17 at different angle (speaking delegates are shown); May 30, 1983
- 1983 Convention-Old Camera, Monday 5/30/83, Morning and Afternoon. (Box 52, Folder 19)
  VHS; 120 min.; Tracking problem first 2 minutes. Podium in focus for 10 minutes before Chaikin calls meeting. Tracking problem returns at 10 minutes. Same content as V15; May 30, 1983
- 1983 Convention-New Camera, Tuesday 5/31/83, Morning Tape #1. (Box 52, Folder 20)
  VHS; 120 min.; Rabbi Robert Frazen, Secretary Daniels, Congressmen James Wright, praises Paula Green and Malcolm Dodd for "Look for the Union Label." VP Sol Hoffman speaks on the Reagan administration, reads the preamble to the report. VP Cornelius Wall discusses minimum wage, shortage of low and middle income housing. Shelley Appleton reads Report of Finances including strike relief and the publication of ILGWU materials in other languages. VP Wall discussing price control for petroleum, utility industry safeguards, labor law reform, homework/labor standards/undocumented workers; May 31, 1983
- 1983 Convention-New Camera, Tuesday 5/31/83, Morning Tape #2, Afternoon Tape #1. (Box 52, Folder 21)
  VHS; 120 min.; Congressman James Wright discusses Reagan. Secretary Daniels makes announcements. Chaikin resumes. Negotiation committee changes in the composition of the GEB; May 31, 1983
- 1983 Convention- New Camera, Tuesday 5/31/1983 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  VHS; 120 min.; May 31, 1983
- 1983 Convention- Old Camera, Tuesday 5/31/1983 (Box 52, Folder 23)
- 1983 Convention- Old Camera, Wednesday 6/1/1983 (Box 52, Folder 24)
  VHS; 120 min.; June 1, 1983
- 1983 Convention New Camera, Wednesday 6/1/1983 (Box 52, Folder 25)
- 1983 Convention- New Camera, Wednesday, 6/1/1983 (Box 52, Folder 26)
- 1983 Convention- New Camera, Tuesday 6/2/1983 (Box 52, Folder 27)
  VHS; 120 min.; June 2, 1983
- 1983 Convention- New Camera, Wednesday 6/1/1983 (Box 52, Folder 28)
- 1983 Convention- New Camera. Wednesday 6/1/1983 (Box 52, Folder 29)
  VHS; 120 min.; June 1 1983
- 1983 Convention Old Camera, Thursday 6/2/1983 (Box 52, Folder 30)
- 1983 Convention- New Camera, Friday 6/3/1983 (Box 52, Folder 31)
  VHS; 120 min.; June 3, 1983
- 1983 Convention- New Camera, Friday 6/3/1983 (Box 52, Folder 32)
- 1983 Convention- Old Camera, Friday 6/3/1983 (Box 52, Folder 33)
- 1983 Convention- Old Camera, Friday 6/3/1983 (Box 52, Folder 34)
- ILGWU "Teleconference Montage" about imports, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 254)
  June; Channel 4 news story on the effects of imports; interviews factory works who lost their jobs. ABC Eyewitness News story, and a CBS- Boston story. Then "Nationwide Teleconference" interviews with plant managers and the Mayor of Fall River, MA. Chaikin speaks as moderator. Evelyn Dubrow announces the Rangel/Moynihan resolutions to imports in US markets. Speaker of the House Thomas P. "Tip" O'Neill, speaks on behalf of the legislation.
- Convention 1983; WPLG And WCKT TV News Miami, Hollywood FLA. (Box 53, Folder 255)
- Sol Chaikin on CBS News - history of ILGWU and problem with imports, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 256)
- Miscellaneous News, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 257)
  Competitive advantage held by foreign manufacturers paying low wages, Japanese representative says that Japan has the same problem.
- Senator Mondale with David Brinkley, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 258)
- Senator Mondale with David Brinkley, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 258)
  3/4" U-Matic; 30 min.; September 1983
- Jane Whitney Show, Philadelphia; Buy American, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 259)
  March; about exported jobs and unemployment
- Sweatshops (Box 53, Folder 260)
  September 8; Union and non-Union sweatshops visited, unsanitary, unsafe, Mafia suspected in trucking industry overcharging.
- ILGWU Ike Pappa - CBS Morning News, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 261)
  June 3
- Governor Mario Cuomo Endorsed (over Mayor Ed Koch) by ILGWU President Sol Chaikin (Box 53, Folder 262)
- PM Magazine profile, WDVM-TV Washington, DC (Ch. 9) on Evy (Evelyn) Dubrow, Queen of the lobbyists; talks to legislators and WDC staff, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 263)
  April; Union Label Commercial; tracking problem 1st 30 sec; Missing
- PM Magazine profile, WDVM-TV Washington D.C. (Channel 9) on Evelyn Dubrow, Queen of the lobbyists; talks to legislators and Washington, D.C. staff. Union Label commercial, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 263)
  3/4" U-Matic; April 1982
- Solidarity Day Protest March on WDC (Box 53, Folder 264)
  September; ILGWU Chorus, News Shows, President Reagan's Labor Policies; [web has Sept. 19, 1981]
- Solidarity Day Protest March on WDC. ILGWU Chorus, News Shows, President Reagans Labor Policies. (Box 53, Folder 264)
  3/4" U-Matic; 10 min.; September 8
- Union Label Chorus. Atlanta auditions and interviews about the impact of ILGWU in their lives., 1979 (Box 53, Folder 265)
  3/4 " U-Matic; 3 min.; October 1979
- Atlanta auditions and interviews about the impact of ILGWU in their lives, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 265)
  Union Label Chorus
- Issues Campaign Spots. Education, Jobs Taxes, Health Rights, Minorities., 1984 (Box 53, Folder 266)
  3/4 " U-Matic; 30 sec.
- Issues Campaign Spots. Education, Jobs Taxes, Health Rights, Minorities., 1984 (Box 53, Folder 266)
- Public Service Announcements (Box 53, Folder 267)
- Public Service Announcements. (Box 53, Folder 267)
  3/4" U-MATIC; 14.6 min.
- [No title] (Box 53, Folder 268)
  16mm; 9.2 min.
- [No title] (Box 53, Folder 269)
- [No title] (Box 53, Folder 270)
  16mm; 9.2 min
- C1- NBC News brief on David Dubinskys death. C2- CBS News story, same subject, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 271)
  September 29; C2- pictures and colors not stable throughout
- CBS Evening News with Dan Rather new story on David Dubinskys death, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 272)
  September 29; C2 is in better condition as C1
- NBC Local News story on David Dubinskys death, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 273)
  September 29; C1 better than C2
- NBC Local News with Chuck Scarborough - story on David Dubinskys death, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 274)
- NBC Nightly News story on David Dubinskys death, 1682 (Box 54, Folder 275)
  September 17
- Channel 7 Eyewitness News- story on David Dubinskys death, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 276)
- WOR-TV Noon News- Story on David Dubinskys death, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 277)
- WPIX-TV INDEPENDENT NETWORK NEWS- Story on David Dubinskys death, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 278)
- "David Dubinsky Dies" - Del Frank reporting, 1982 (Box 55, Folder 279)
  September 29; does not play
- "David Dubinsky Dies." Paula Green Advertising, 1982 (Box 55, Folder 280)
  September 19; same as 279; color is worse
- Local 23-25 Chinatown Rally 1, 1982 (Box 55, Folder 281)
  Tape 1, early arrivals, Union Label song (Chinese and English), Jay Mazur, Shui Mak Ka
- Local 23-25 Chinatown rally 2, 1982 (Box 55, Folder 282)
  Tape 1, Jay Mazur, Shui Mak Ka, Sol Chaikin, Alice Tse, and off-air television coverage
- Local 23-25 Chinatown Rally 1 Tape 3, 1982 (Box 55, Folder 283)
  June 24; cutaways; street before rally and inside park, phone bank, ILGWU van driving through streets of NY Cit; no sound
- Local 23-25 Chinatown Rally 1 Tape 2, 1982 (Box 55, Folder 284)
  June 24; Lily Moy, Sol Chaikin, Harry Van Arsdale, Jr., Margaret Fung, Yuk Lai Leu, Kathy Andrade, and Kai P. Wong.
- Local 23-25 Chinatown Rally 2 Tape 2, 1982 (Box 55, Folder 285)
  July 15; inside park, Canal Street during march; Tape sticks out of cassette
- Local 23-25 Chinatown Rally 2 Tape 3, 1982 (Box 55, Folder 286)
  July 15; film-tape transfer (both rallies and march); video grainy; no sound
- Sol Chaikin - Democratic Response to Reagans State of the Union Address CBS-TV, 1983 (Box 56, Folder 35)
  January 23; VHS
- Gus Tyler - "New York People", 1983 (Box 56, Folder 36)
  April 21; Live at Five - Ch. 4, SCC - Cable News Network; VHS
- "Miles of Smiles, Years of Struggles," "Can we afford retirement?" and "Once upon a time" (Box 56, Folder 37)
  WNET Labor Day
- Phillips Center, Interviewer training, Parts 1-3 (Box 56, Folder 38)
  VHS; 120 min.
- The State of the Union: A Democratic View. DH Sawyer and Associates, 1983 (Box 56, Folder 39)
  VHS; 21.8 min.; January 26, 1983
- 5AM America; Donovan and Sol Chaikin (Box 56, Folder 39a)
- Under His Thumb (Box 56, Folder 288)
  3/4" U-Matic; 30 min.; WPXI-TV Pittsbugh
- Sol Chaikin Interview, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 289)
  July 9
- Sol Chaikin Speech at the Democratic National Convention, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 290)
  August 27; Madison Square Garden, NY
- Sol Chaikin Speech at the Democratic National Convention, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 290)
  3/4" U-Matic; Madison Square Garden, New York City, August 27, 1980
- Minimum wage, Should Kids Get Less?, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 291)
  3/4" U-Matic, 30 min.; December 2, 1980
- Sol Chaikin - ILGWU CNN-TV (Box 56, Folder 292)
  September 6
- Sol Chaikin - ILGWU (Box 56, Folder 293)
  September 6; ABC, Good Morning America
- Mini Documentary on ILGWU Lino Manocchia Channel 47 (Box 56, Folder 294)
- Sol Chaikin, President of ILGWU, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 295)
  August 5; Good Morning America over ABC TV
- Sol Chaikin, President Of ILGWU, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 296)
- Straight talk, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 297)
  3/4" U-Matic; November 18, 1980
- Sol Goldberg - Focus on NJ (Box 56, Folder 298)
- Summer Semester Program #1 SCC Phil Doke (Box 56, Folder 299)
- Television Clips; Labor Day, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 40)
  Sol Chaikin/Abe Raskin; VHS
- In-House Polling: A New Technique For Organizing. (Box 57, Folder 41)
- Starobin, Ch. 5 News; Sol Chaikin, Ch.2 News, 1982-1983 (Box 57, Folder 42)
  December 2 and January 11; VHS
- "The Last Word" on Medicare $ + Union Organizing (Box 57, Folder 43)
  January 31; Barbaro - ABC; VHS
- 20/20 - Sweatshops (Box 57, Folder 44)
- Ch. 41 News - Amy Gonzales; Ch.2 Starobin, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 45)
  July 30 and September 13; VHS
- Labor Video Bulletin #3: "Labor in the Computer Age," "America Works," "Unions: On the Air" by the Labor Institute of Public Affairs (Box 57, Folder 46)
  VHS; 25 min.; Labor Institute of Public Affairs
- Labor Video Bulletin #4: "The Video Bulletin Update," "Regional Conference: Los Angeles," "Solidarity Day III Report" by the Labor Institute of Public Affairs (Box 57, Folder 47)
- Houston Organizing Project, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 48)
  March 5; NBC-TV; VHS
- Labor Video Bulletin #1: VFW/SEUI Organizing Drive, Community Services Conference, Legislative Report "Unemployment Up and I'm Down" by the Labor Institute of Public Affairs (Box 57, Folder 49)